(Bernadette:)But you could
if you wanted to, right?
(Penny:)Well, yeah, I guess.
(Bernadette:)Pick out the hottest guy
in the room,
(Bernadette:)take him home,
do unspeakable things to him,
(Bernadette:)then kick him to the curb
with a smile on his face
(Bernadette:)and teeth marks on his heinie?
(Penny:)More or less.
(Amy:)What's that like?
(Leonard:)I don't know.
(Penny:)It's fun while
you're doing it.
(Penny:)And then after,
it's mostly embarrassment,
(Penny:)self-loathing
and regret.
(Bernadette:)I would take that deal
all day long.
(Penny:)Yeah, well, it's not
gonna happen tonight.
(Penny:)You know, for the
first time in my life,
(Penny:)I am not
in a relationship,
(Penny:)and I'm totally
okay with it.
(Amy:)You know, if being on
your own is new to you,
(Amy:)I'd be happy to share some
tension-relieving techniques
(Amy:)for ladies I've perfected
over the years.
(Amy:)For example, do you have
an electric toothbrush?
PENNY:
Um, no.
(Amy:)You should get one.
(Bernadette:)What's that?
(Amy:)It appears
to be something preserved